<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv source-info-url="https://elcinema.com/en/tvguide/" source-info-name="elCinema.com" generator-info-name="Manus EPG Generator">
  <channel id="mbc max">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc max</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="mbc 2">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc 2</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251219140000 +0800" stop="20251219163000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">12 Strong</title>
    <desc lang="en">Based on a true story, the film tells the story of a SpecialForces team that was sent to Afghanistan right after the 9/11 attacks. Deep into enemy territory, the team faces unfavorable odds and make uneasy alliances as they try to take down the Taliban.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219163000 +0800" stop="20251219183000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Rogue</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Samantha O'Hara leads a team of mercenaries on a missionto rescue hostages in remote Africa, the mission goes haywire and the team becomes hunted by a group of rebels and wild lions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2020)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219183000 +0800" stop="20251219203000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Transporter 3</title>
    <desc lang="en">Frank Martin finds himself tasked with transporting theEnvironmental Agency Minister's daughter under dangerous circumstances.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2008)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219203000 +0800" stop="20251219223000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Transporter Refueled</title>
    <desc lang="en">When former mercenary-turned-contract driver Frank Martin ishired by a mysterious woman for a job, he finds himself embroiled in a dangerous game, since the woman has her own vendetta that she wants to settle with a Russian mobster.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219223000 +0800" stop="20251220010000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Man on Fire</title>
    <desc lang="en">Based in Mexico, ex-FBI agent John Creasy is hired toprotect nine-year-old Pita Ramos, who gets kidnapped. Creasy swears to stop at nothing to get revenge from her kidnappers.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2004)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220010000 +0800" stop="20251220033000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Captain Phillips</title>
    <desc lang="en">This thriller recounts how the U.S. container ship, theMaersk Alabama, headed by Captain Richard Phillips (Tom Hanks), became the first American ship to be hijacked in two hundred years when they come head to head with Somali pirates.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220033000 +0800" stop="20251220053000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Good German</title>
    <desc lang="en">When an American war correspondent arrives in post-warBerlin to report on a conference, he is drawn into a murder investigation and an attempt to help his former sweetheart escape Germany which uncovers a larger government conspiracy.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220053000 +0800" stop="20251220080000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">12 Strong</title>
    <desc lang="en">Based on a true story, the film tells the story of a SpecialForces team that was sent to Afghanistan right after the 9/11 attacks. Deep into enemy territory, the team faces unfavorable odds and make uneasy alliances as they try to take down the Taliban.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220080000 +0800" stop="20251220100000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Debt Collector</title>
    <desc lang="en">Looking for a job in America, a British martial artist landsone as a mob debt collector, but when a job goes south, he gets dragged into trouble, fighting to find his way out of it while questioning the rightness of what he's doing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220100000 +0800" stop="20251220120000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Debt Collectors</title>
    <desc lang="en">The debt collectors, French and Sue, find themselves facingall kinds of trouble, when they do a job in Las Vegas that leads them to chasing down a dirty casino owner while evading a vengeful drug kingpin.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2020)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220120000 +0800" stop="20251220140000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Atomic Blonde</title>
    <desc lang="en">On the eve of the fall of the Berlin wall, spy LorraineBroughton goes on a mission to bring down the spy network that killed an undercover agent for an unknown reason.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220140000 +0800" stop="20251220160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Mechanic</title>
    <desc lang="en">An elite hitman is successful working in the shadows. Nowhe's teaching his trade to an apprentice who is related to one of his previous victims.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220160000 +0800" stop="20251220173000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Mile 22</title>
    <desc lang="en">Assigned to Indonesia, a top notch intelligence officer,backed up by top-secret tactical command unit, is commissioned to smuggle a police officer out of the country, as he has some sensitive and classified information.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220173000 +0800" stop="20251220200000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Captain Phillips</title>
    <desc lang="en">This thriller recounts how the U.S. container ship, theMaersk Alabama, headed by Captain Richard Phillips (Tom Hanks), became the first American ship to be hijacked in two hundred years when they come head to head with Somali pirates.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220200000 +0800" stop="20251220220000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Rogue</title>
    <desc lang="en">As Samantha O'Hara leads a team of mercenaries on a missionto rescue hostages in remote Africa, the mission goes haywire and the team becomes hunted by a group of rebels and wild lions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2020)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220220000 +0800" stop="20251220233000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Faster</title>
    <desc lang="en">Driver (Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson) seeks revenge againstthose who put him in prison as well as those who killed his brother. After 10 years, he is released from prison, drives through the deserts of Nevada in search of his enemies while being chased by a contract killer (Oliver Jackson-Cohen) and a veteran cop (Billy Bob Thornton).</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2010)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220233000 +0800" stop="20251221013000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Rescue Dawn</title>
    <desc lang="en">A German/American plane goes out on a secret mission, butcrashes in a forest during the Laos bombing of 1965. The plane's crew are taken as hostages and tortured by Vietcong forces. US Navy Pilot successfully plans an escape method for the hostages, but they face plenty of unforeseen events.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221013000 +0800" stop="20251221033000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Love &amp; Mercy</title>
    <desc lang="en">Following Brian Wilson, the front man of the famous bandBeach Boys, in two decades: in the 1960's while struggling with psychosis and writing his avante-pop masterpiece, and in the 1980's, while he is officially a patient suffering from mental illness under the watch of therapist Eugene Landy.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221033000 +0800" stop="20251221060000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Amazing Spider-Man</title>
    <desc lang="en">Peter Parker and Gwen have been together since high school.Peter discovers a mysterious briefcase that used to be his father's, and when he decides to investigate, he is drawn into a world that makes a super-hero out of him. He fights evil in all its forms, with his super abilities that have generated thanks to a genetically-modified spider's bite.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221060000 +0800" stop="20251221080000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Mile 22</title>
    <desc lang="en">Assigned to Indonesia, a top notch intelligence officer,backed up by top-secret tactical command unit, is commissioned to smuggle a police officer out of the country, as he has some sensitive and classified information.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221080000 +0800" stop="20251221100000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">After Earth</title>
    <desc lang="en">Will Smith and son Jaden co-star as the legendary Cypher andson Kitai, who crash land on an abandoned Earth a millennium after humanity's escape. With Cypher injured, teenage Kitai has to brave the hostile environment, brimming with aggressive evolved animal species and aliens, on his own to look for help.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221100000 +0800" stop="20251221120000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Snowpiercer</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a failed climate-change experiment , ice age destroyslife on the planet except some survivors, who take a huge train (Snowpiercer) as a place of survival. The elite live at the front, while the poor live at the back. But 17 years later, the tail's inhabitants start a rebellion led by Curtis (Chris Evans).</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221120000 +0800" stop="20251221140000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">R.I.P.D.</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a force of undead police officers, the Rest in PeaceDepartment, a young slain cop (Ryan Reynolds) teams up with veteran sheriff (Jeff Bridges) to protect the living from roving, monstrous spirits who have not yet crossed over.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221140000 +0800" stop="20251221160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Total Recall</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a world devastated by a global war, except for WesternEurope (UFB) and Australia (the Colony), Douglas Quaid believes he is a factory worker until he discovers real memories of being a high-profile agent at UFB after visiting Rekall, a recreational company that implants false memories. A series of chases and clues reveal the plan to eliminate the Colony and only Quaid can "kill" the plan.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221160000 +0800" stop="20251221180000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Last Witch Hunter</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, Kaulder is the last witch hunter remaining, and hasspent centuries hunting down rogue witches, all the while yearning for his long-lost loved ones. However, unbeknownst to Kaulder, the Queen Witch is resurrected and seeks revenge on her killer causing an epic battle that will determine the survival of the human race.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221180000 +0800" stop="20251221200000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Atomic Blonde</title>
    <desc lang="en">On the eve of the fall of the Berlin wall, spy LorraineBroughton goes on a mission to bring down the spy network that killed an undercover agent for an unknown reason.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221200000 +0800" stop="20251221213000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Mile 22</title>
    <desc lang="en">Assigned to Indonesia, a top notch intelligence officer,backed up by top-secret tactical command unit, is commissioned to smuggle a police officer out of the country, as he has some sensitive and classified information.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221213000 +0800" stop="20251221233000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Mechanic</title>
    <desc lang="en">An elite hitman is successful working in the shadows. Nowhe's teaching his trade to an apprentice who is related to one of his previous victims.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221233000 +0800" stop="20251222010000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Debt Collector</title>
    <desc lang="en">Looking for a job in America, a British martial artist landsone as a mob debt collector, but when a job goes south, he gets dragged into trouble, fighting to find his way out of it while questioning the rightness of what he's doing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219130000 +0800" stop="20251219150000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Battle: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc lang="en">The US marines face off against alien creatures who areattempting an invasion of the city of LA.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219150000 +0800" stop="20251219170000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Mortal Kombat</title>
    <desc lang="en">When a young hero gets embroiled in a brutal,multi-dimensional battle, the experience gives him a new perspective on his limits and capabilities.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219170000 +0800" stop="20251219183000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Underworld: Rise of the Lycans</title>
    <desc lang="en">In continuation of the first two parts of the same series,bloody events unfold between bloodsucking vampires and their slaves, the Lycans. The Lycans are led by Lucian, who wants to destroy the vampires' leader, whose daughter is in love with Lucian. She joins in the bloody wars with her lover against her father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219183000 +0800" stop="20251219203000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Space Jam: A New Legacy</title>
    <desc lang="en">After NBA superstar LeBron James finds himself trapped withhis son in a virtual space, he must join forces with Bugs Bunny and the rest of the Looney Tunes gang to win a fateful basketball game against the Goon Squad and get back home with his son.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219203000 +0800" stop="20251219221500 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Smurfs 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Smurfette is kidnapped by the evil wizard Gargamel, herlittle blue cohorts rally their human friends to help rescue her. And the stakes are high, as she has discovered a secret spell that can turn Gargamel's newest creation, creatures called the Naughties, into real Smurfs.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251219221500 +0800" stop="20251220000000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Mirrors</title>
    <desc lang="en">A New York detective takes over night duty to secure a storethat has been shut down due to a large fire. He is exposed to strange happenings during the night. His wife is affected as well, and it becomes his duty to protect her and their son.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2008)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220000000 +0800" stop="20251220013000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">I Used to Go Here</title>
    <desc lang="en">Right after her new novel is published, the 35-year-old Kateis invited by her professor to speak at her alma matter, but little did Kate know that her journey will get her involved with a group of college students.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2020)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220013000 +0800" stop="20251220040000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Freaks</title>
    <desc lang="en">After being confined to living in an abandoned house withher father for fear of being killed, seven-year-old Chloe comes outside only to discover that she possess abnormal power, which puts her life in danger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220040000 +0800" stop="20251220060000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Kung Fu Panda</title>
    <desc lang="en">Po panda finds himself chosen to fight the enemies, despitethe fact that he is obese and fairly lazy. He tries to prove himself in front of Master Shifu and the legendary Furious Five.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie - Cartoon
               (2008)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220060000 +0800" stop="20251220083000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Battle: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc lang="en">The US marines face off against alien creatures who areattempting an invasion of the city of LA.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220083000 +0800" stop="20251220110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Hugo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In 1930's Paris, orphaned Hugo lives in a crowded trainstation. He enters a new adventure with Isabelle, in an attempt to solve the mystery his father has left behind regarding an automaton.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220110000 +0800" stop="20251220130000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Jack the Giant Slayer</title>
    <desc lang="en">An ancient war is reignited when a young farmhand, Jack,unwittingly opens a gateway between our world and that of a fearsome race of giants. Jack fights for a kingdom, its people, and the love of a princess.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220130000 +0800" stop="20251220150000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Huntsman: Winter's War</title>
    <desc lang="en">Raised as soldiers in Ice Queen Freya's army, Eric and Sara,a fellow warrior, attempt to hide their forbidden love while they battle to survive Freya and her sister Ravenna's evil plans.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2016)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220150000 +0800" stop="20251220170000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">King Arthur: Legend of the Sword</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of young King Arthur who succeeded in drawing thepowerful sword of Excalibur from the rock  where it is lodged. He has to control his sword and unite the people under one front in order to defeat the tyrannical Vortigern, who had killed his parents and seized his throne in the past.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220170000 +0800" stop="20251220190000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">47 Ronin</title>
    <desc lang="en">This action epic brings to life the real tale of 47 samuraiwarriors who in 18th century Japan set out on a quest to avenge the death of their master, killed by a treacherous overlord who banished them from their homeland.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220190000 +0800" stop="20251220210000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Freaks</title>
    <desc lang="en">After being confined to living in an abandoned house withher father for fear of being killed, seven-year-old Chloe comes outside only to discover that she possess abnormal power, which puts her life in danger.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220210000 +0800" stop="20251220230000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Mortal Kombat</title>
    <desc lang="en">When a young hero gets embroiled in a brutal,multi-dimensional battle, the experience gives him a new perspective on his limits and capabilities.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251220230000 +0800" stop="20251221010000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Blade</title>
    <desc lang="en">Having lost his mother as a child when a vampire killed her,Blade, a half-vampire, half-mortal, takes matters into his own hands as he vows to slay wicked vampires to protect human beings.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (1998)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221010000 +0800" stop="20251221030000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Huntsman: Winter's War</title>
    <desc lang="en">Raised as soldiers in Ice Queen Freya's army, Eric and Sara,a fellow warrior, attempt to hide their forbidden love while they battle to survive Freya and her sister Ravenna's evil plans.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2016)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221030000 +0800" stop="20251221050000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Jack the Giant Slayer</title>
    <desc lang="en">An ancient war is reignited when a young farmhand, Jack,unwittingly opens a gateway between our world and that of a fearsome race of giants. Jack fights for a kingdom, its people, and the love of a princess.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221050000 +0800" stop="20251221070000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">47 Ronin</title>
    <desc lang="en">This action epic brings to life the real tale of 47 samuraiwarriors who in 18th century Japan set out on a quest to avenge the death of their master, killed by a treacherous overlord who banished them from their homeland.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221070000 +0800" stop="20251221090000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">King Arthur: Legend of the Sword</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of young King Arthur who succeeded in drawing thepowerful sword of Excalibur from the rock  where it is lodged. He has to control his sword and unite the people under one front in order to defeat the tyrannical Vortigern, who had killed his parents and seized his throne in the past.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221090000 +0800" stop="20251221110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Get Smart</title>
    <desc lang="en">Maxwell Smart is an analyst at an American intelligenceagency who years for something more: he wants to become a field agent. Smart is promoted and partnered up with Agent 99. However, a number of comical situations occur due to Smart's lack of proper training.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2008)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221110000 +0800" stop="20251221130000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Duplicity</title>
    <desc lang="en">The rivalry between Ray and Claire, whether in their rolesas government officials or later as industrial employees, gives rise to a whirlwind romance that leaves them plotting their own heist.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221130000 +0800" stop="20251221153000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Knives Out</title>
    <desc lang="en">When the body of crime novelist Harlan Thrombey is found,Detective Benoit Blanc takes charge of the crime investigation and finds himself involved in numerous events in search of the truth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221153000 +0800" stop="20251221170000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Nobody</title>
    <desc lang="en">After an incident in which he failed to protect his family,Hutch is unable to deal with the distance it results in, which only fuels his determination to protect a woman when she gets harassed. But as the confrontation earns him the wrath of a drug lord, he fights to protect himself and his family.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221170000 +0800" stop="20251221190000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">CHIPS</title>
    <desc lang="en">Frank Poncherello, an undercover federal agent, and JonBaker, a rookie, join the highway patrol in California for entirely different reasons. They team up and roam around putting a stop to speeding cars and vehicle thefts, helping those who are lost, and investigating crimes.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221190000 +0800" stop="20251221210000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Jack the Giant Slayer</title>
    <desc lang="en">An ancient war is reignited when a young farmhand, Jack,unwittingly opens a gateway between our world and that of a fearsome race of giants. Jack fights for a kingdom, its people, and the love of a princess.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221210000 +0800" stop="20251221230000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">King Arthur: Legend of the Sword</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of young King Arthur who succeeded in drawing thepowerful sword of Excalibur from the rock  where it is lodged. He has to control his sword and unite the people under one front in order to defeat the tyrannical Vortigern, who had killed his parents and seized his throne in the past.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221230000 +0800" stop="20251222010000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Hugo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In 1930's Paris, orphaned Hugo lives in a crowded trainstation. He enters a new adventure with Isabelle, in an attempt to solve the mystery his father has left behind regarding an automaton.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
</tv>
