<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv source-info-url="https://elcinema.com/en/tvguide/" source-info-name="elCinema.com" generator-info-name="Manus EPG Generator">
  <channel id="mbc max">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc max</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="mbc 2">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc 2</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251227093000 +0800" stop="20251227120000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr. Adrian Helmsley is an American geologist who, while on atrip to India, learns that there has been increased solar activity. Dr. Helmsley also discovers that this will lead to a rise in the temperature of Earth’s core – a phenomenon which will have dire consequences for humanity. 2012 is said to be the end date of the Mayan calendar, which many believe marks the end of the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227120000 +0800" stop="20251227140000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Into the Storm</title>
    <desc lang="en">The town of Silverton is devastated by a wave of deadlytornadoes, and storm trackers predict the worst is yet to come. Meanwhile, a group of high school students document the events and aftermath of the disaster.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227140000 +0800" stop="20251227160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Impossible</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young British family vacationing in Thailand is suddenlytorn apart when the devastating 2004 tsunami tears through their seaside resort. Their devoted search for one another is a testament to the human spirit and the power of family.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227160000 +0800" stop="20251227173000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Adrift</title>
    <desc lang="en">The true story of, Tami Oldham and Richard Sharp, whosailed across the ocean, but didn't anticipate that they would be sailing directly into one of the most catastrophic hurricanes in recorded history and must stand against all difficulties throughout their journey.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227173000 +0800" stop="20251227200000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Public Enemies</title>
    <desc lang="en">A biopic that chronicles the FBI hunt of the infamous thiefJohn Dillinger and two of his known associates, Baby Face Nelson and Pretty Boy Floyd.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227200000 +0800" stop="20251227213000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Eastern Promises</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a London hospital, a Russian teenager dies while givingbirth, and the midwife finds her diary that contains clues leading to a Russian mob family that has assaulted her.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2007)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227213000 +0800" stop="20251227233000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Lucky Number Slevin</title>
    <desc lang="en">A case of mistaken identity lands Slevin in the middle of awar between two rival crime bosses. Put under surveillance by a detective and an assassin, he has to plan his move before they make their own.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227233000 +0800" stop="20251228013000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Paddington 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Paddington is happily living with the Brown family inWindsor Gardens, where he becomes a popular member of the community. He finds a special book to give to his Aunt Lucy for her 100th birthday at Mr. Gruber's antique shop, and gets involved in a series of peculiar jobs to buy it.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228013000 +0800" stop="20251228040000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Impossible</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young British family vacationing in Thailand is suddenlytorn apart when the devastating 2004 tsunami tears through their seaside resort. Their devoted search for one another is a testament to the human spirit and the power of family.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228040000 +0800" stop="20251228060000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Into the Storm</title>
    <desc lang="en">The town of Silverton is devastated by a wave of deadlytornadoes, and storm trackers predict the worst is yet to come. Meanwhile, a group of high school students document the events and aftermath of the disaster.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228060000 +0800" stop="20251228080000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Adrift</title>
    <desc lang="en">The true story of, Tami Oldham and Richard Sharp, whosailed across the ocean, but didn't anticipate that they would be sailing directly into one of the most catastrophic hurricanes in recorded history and must stand against all difficulties throughout their journey.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228080000 +0800" stop="20251228100000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Line of Duty</title>
    <desc lang="en">After accidentally killing a child abductor, the disgracedcop Frank Penny enters a race against time to find the daughter of the police chief before it's too late.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228100000 +0800" stop="20251228120000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">211</title>
    <desc lang="en">When a group of ex-mercenaries carry out a risky bank heist,police detectives Steve MacAvoy and Mike Chandler find themselves dreadfully unprepared.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228120000 +0800" stop="20251228140000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Non-Stop</title>
    <desc lang="en">The movie is set in an international flight from New York toLondon. During that trip, Bill Marks (Liam Neeson) receives several threats from an unknown threat that every 20 minutes a passenger will be killed unless $ 150 million is transferred to a bank account. The twist occurs when the owner of this account is revealed.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228140000 +0800" stop="20251228160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Bullet Head</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a robbery goes south, three criminals hide from thepolice in a warehouse. Unbeknownst to them, a bigger threat awaits them inside, forcing them into a fight for survival.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228160000 +0800" stop="20251228180000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Those Who Wish Me Dead</title>
    <desc lang="en">A thriller that sees a teenager who witnessed a murder andis now pursued by two ruthless assassins who chase him into the Montana wilderness, with only a survival expert as his protector. But can his protector save him from a forest fire so fierce that it can consume them all?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227090000 +0800" stop="20251227110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Arthur</title>
    <desc lang="en">Arthur ( Russell Brand), a drunken playboy is forced by hismother to marry the successful businesswoman Susan or he will lose his inheritance. But he meets the outgoing girl Naomi, he thinks that she's the one, and he has to choose between love or fortune.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227110000 +0800" stop="20251227130000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Tower Heist</title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of men who work at a tower discover that they arevictims of a wealthy businessman, and that they are part of a plan to steal the tower.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227130000 +0800" stop="20251227150000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Horrible Bosses 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Nick, Dale and Curt decide to open their own business,they discover an investor who is trying to take them down. So they decide to kidnap his son Rex, to put up a ransom to take back their business.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227150000 +0800" stop="20251227170000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Vacation</title>
    <desc lang="en">In an attempt to reconnect with his family, Rusty Griswoldtakes his wife and sons on a road trip, hoping it will send them journeying through their relationship, but things go unexpectedly odd.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227170000 +0800" stop="20251227183000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Unfinished Business</title>
    <desc lang="en">A hard-working small business owner and his two associatestravel to Europe to close the most important deal of their lives. But what began as a routine business trip goes off the rails in every imaginable and unimaginable way.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227183000 +0800" stop="20251227203000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">In the Line of Fire</title>
    <desc lang="en">An aging secret service agent who suffers from the aftermathof the John F. Kennedy assassination in Dallas, receives calls from an unstable man telling him information about his plans to assassinate the current president.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (1993)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227203000 +0800" stop="20251227233000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Equalizer</title>
    <desc lang="en">McCall (Denzel Washington) is a former black ops commandowho has faked his death to live a quiet life in Boston. When he comes out of his self-imposed retirement to rescue a young girl, Teri (Chloë Grace Moretz), he finds himself face to face with notorious Russian gangsters. As he serves vengeance against those who brutalize the helpless, McCall's desire for justice is reawakened.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227233000 +0800" stop="20251228010000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Vengeance: A Love Story</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a woman was physically assaulted by a group of peopleafter attending a party and getting away with it, John Dromoor, a gulf war veteran who now works as a local police officer decides to take matters into his own hands and bring the woman justice.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228010000 +0800" stop="20251228030000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Five Feet Apart</title>
    <desc lang="en">Stella is a cystic fibrosis patient who spends her days inthe hospital, without anything exciting about her life, until she meets the rebellious Will who suffers from the same illness and they both change each other's lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228030000 +0800" stop="20251228050000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Tower Heist</title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of men who work at a tower discover that they arevictims of a wealthy businessman, and that they are part of a plan to steal the tower.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228050000 +0800" stop="20251228070000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">My Super Ex-Girlfriend</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Matt dumps Jenny, who is on the needy side, she usesher superpowers to make his life miserable.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228070000 +0800" stop="20251228090000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Bedazzled</title>
    <desc lang="en">Elliot is desperate to win the heart of his dream girlAllison,  he is offered seven wishes by a very persuasive Devil to have what he wants, but in return he must give her his soul.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2000)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228090000 +0800" stop="20251228110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Dark Tower</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a parallel universe, Roland Deschain fights witheverything he has to prevent his enemy, the Man in Black, from bringing down a structure that preserves reality. With the Man in Black trying to use psychic children to unleash darkness, Roland takes one of them in to save both him and the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228110000 +0800" stop="20251228133000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Warcraft</title>
    <desc lang="en">Using a magic portal, an Orc horde is invading the planetAzeroth, and a small group of human heroes and dissident Orcs are fighting to stop the real evil that is causing this war.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2016)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228133000 +0800" stop="20251228153000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Sicario</title>
    <desc lang="en">In the border stretching between Mexico and the U.S.A., anarea that has been always out of the reach of the law, an idealistic FBI agent is assigned to aid in the escalating war against the cartel.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228153000 +0800" stop="20251228173000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Sicario: Day of the Soldado</title>
    <desc lang="en">In this sequel to the 2015 film Sicario, the drug war on theUS-Mexico border has escalated as the cartels have begun trafficking terrorists across the US border.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
</tv>
