<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv source-info-url="https://elcinema.com/en/tvguide/" source-info-name="elCinema.com" generator-info-name="Manus EPG Generator">
  <channel id="mbc max">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc max</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="mbc 2">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc 2</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251221140000 +0800" stop="20251221160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Total Recall</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a world devastated by a global war, except for WesternEurope (UFB) and Australia (the Colony), Douglas Quaid believes he is a factory worker until he discovers real memories of being a high-profile agent at UFB after visiting Rekall, a recreational company that implants false memories. A series of chases and clues reveal the plan to eliminate the Colony and only Quaid can "kill" the plan.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221160000 +0800" stop="20251221180000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Last Witch Hunter</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, Kaulder is the last witch hunter remaining, and hasspent centuries hunting down rogue witches, all the while yearning for his long-lost loved ones. However, unbeknownst to Kaulder, the Queen Witch is resurrected and seeks revenge on her killer causing an epic battle that will determine the survival of the human race.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221180000 +0800" stop="20251221200000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Atomic Blonde</title>
    <desc lang="en">On the eve of the fall of the Berlin wall, spy LorraineBroughton goes on a mission to bring down the spy network that killed an undercover agent for an unknown reason.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221200000 +0800" stop="20251221213000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Mile 22</title>
    <desc lang="en">Assigned to Indonesia, a top notch intelligence officer,backed up by top-secret tactical command unit, is commissioned to smuggle a police officer out of the country, as he has some sensitive and classified information.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221213000 +0800" stop="20251221233000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Mechanic</title>
    <desc lang="en">An elite hitman is successful working in the shadows. Nowhe's teaching his trade to an apprentice who is related to one of his previous victims.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221233000 +0800" stop="20251222010000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Debt Collector</title>
    <desc lang="en">Looking for a job in America, a British martial artist landsone as a mob debt collector, but when a job goes south, he gets dragged into trouble, fighting to find his way out of it while questioning the rightness of what he's doing.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222010000 +0800" stop="20251222030000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Total Recall</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a world devastated by a global war, except for WesternEurope (UFB) and Australia (the Colony), Douglas Quaid believes he is a factory worker until he discovers real memories of being a high-profile agent at UFB after visiting Rekall, a recreational company that implants false memories. A series of chases and clues reveal the plan to eliminate the Colony and only Quaid can "kill" the plan.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222030000 +0800" stop="20251222050000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">R.I.P.D.</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a force of undead police officers, the Rest in PeaceDepartment, a young slain cop (Ryan Reynolds) teams up with veteran sheriff (Jeff Bridges) to protect the living from roving, monstrous spirits who have not yet crossed over.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222050000 +0800" stop="20251222070000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Last Witch Hunter</title>
    <desc lang="en">Today, Kaulder is the last witch hunter remaining, and hasspent centuries hunting down rogue witches, all the while yearning for his long-lost loved ones. However, unbeknownst to Kaulder, the Queen Witch is resurrected and seeks revenge on her killer causing an epic battle that will determine the survival of the human race.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222070000 +0800" stop="20251222093000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">White House Down</title>
    <desc lang="en">DC police officer Cale is on a White House tour with hisdaughter when it is attacked by armed paramilitary invaders. He must save his daughter and the President of the United States, though the odds are against him.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222093000 +0800" stop="20251222120000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Blackhat</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a case of high-level computer hacking arises, a man isreleased from prison to help American and Chinese authorities pursue a mysterious cyber criminal. The cat-and-mouse chase leads them from the U.S.A to Hong Kong.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222120000 +0800" stop="20251222140000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">American Made</title>
    <desc lang="en">Recruited by the CIA, pilot Barry Seal's mission to provideinformation on communists soon gets him entangled with a drug cartel and arms smugglers.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222140000 +0800" stop="20251222160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Girl in the Spider's Web</title>
    <desc lang="en">Young computer hacker (Lisbeth Salander) and journalist(Mikael Blomkvist) find themselves trapped in a web of spies, cybercriminals and corrupt government officials.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222160000 +0800" stop="20251222180000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Infiltrator</title>
    <desc lang="en">The true story of Customs Service agent Robert Mazur whoexposes a money laundering scheme by legendary drug lord Pablo Escobar</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2016)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221153000 +0800" stop="20251221170000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Nobody</title>
    <desc lang="en">After an incident in which he failed to protect his family,Hutch is unable to deal with the distance it results in, which only fuels his determination to protect a woman when she gets harassed. But as the confrontation earns him the wrath of a drug lord, he fights to protect himself and his family.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221170000 +0800" stop="20251221190000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">CHIPS</title>
    <desc lang="en">Frank Poncherello, an undercover federal agent, and JonBaker, a rookie, join the highway patrol in California for entirely different reasons. They team up and roam around putting a stop to speeding cars and vehicle thefts, helping those who are lost, and investigating crimes.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221190000 +0800" stop="20251221210000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Jack the Giant Slayer</title>
    <desc lang="en">An ancient war is reignited when a young farmhand, Jack,unwittingly opens a gateway between our world and that of a fearsome race of giants. Jack fights for a kingdom, its people, and the love of a princess.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221210000 +0800" stop="20251221230000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">King Arthur: Legend of the Sword</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of young King Arthur who succeeded in drawing thepowerful sword of Excalibur from the rock  where it is lodged. He has to control his sword and unite the people under one front in order to defeat the tyrannical Vortigern, who had killed his parents and seized his throne in the past.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251221230000 +0800" stop="20251222010000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Hugo</title>
    <desc lang="en">In 1930's Paris, orphaned Hugo lives in a crowded trainstation. He enters a new adventure with Isabelle, in an attempt to solve the mystery his father has left behind regarding an automaton.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222010000 +0800" stop="20251222033000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Knives Out</title>
    <desc lang="en">When the body of crime novelist Harlan Thrombey is found,Detective Benoit Blanc takes charge of the crime investigation and finds himself involved in numerous events in search of the truth.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222033000 +0800" stop="20251222053000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Duplicity</title>
    <desc lang="en">The rivalry between Ray and Claire, whether in their rolesas government officials or later as industrial employees, gives rise to a whirlwind romance that leaves them plotting their own heist.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222053000 +0800" stop="20251222073000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Burlesque</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a struggling burlesque club that is teetering on the edgeof closing, the owner, Tess, finds a possible saving grace in the arrival of Ali, a small-town girl who possesses a tremendous talent that she soon becomes the club's main attraction.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2010)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222073000 +0800" stop="20251222090000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Kung Fu Panda</title>
    <desc lang="en">Po panda finds himself chosen to fight the enemies, despitethe fact that he is obese and fairly lazy. He tries to prove himself in front of Master Shifu and the legendary Furious Five.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie - Cartoon
               (2008)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222090000 +0800" stop="20251222110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Chasing Mavericks</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Jay Moriarity discovers that the biggest wave inEarth's history, the Mavericks surf break, is approaching his home in Santa Cruz, he seeks help from local hero Frosty Hesson to train him to survive it.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222110000 +0800" stop="20251222133000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Walk</title>
    <desc lang="en">The true story of how a French street performer undertookthe daunting task of walking a tightrope between the Twin Towers of the World Trade Center, all with the aid of a misfit group that he put together</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222133000 +0800" stop="20251222153000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Prizefighter: The Life of Jem Belcher</title>
    <desc lang="en">A biopic about English bare-knuckle prizefighter JemBelcher, shedding light on his journey to become the Champion of All England.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2022)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251222153000 +0800" stop="20251222173000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Fighter</title>
    <desc lang="en">The life story of Mickey Ward, and his relationship with hisbrother Dicky, who is more famous than him in the boxing ring, as well as his exposure to a world of poverty, crime and drugs.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2010)</category>
  </programme>
</tv>
