<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv source-info-url="https://elcinema.com/en/tvguide/" source-info-name="elCinema.com" generator-info-name="Manus EPG Generator">
  <channel id="mbc max">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc max</display-name>
  </channel>
  <channel id="mbc 2">
    <display-name lang="zh">mbc 2</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20251226230000 +0800" stop="20251227010000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Blended</title>
    <desc lang="en">After their blind date goes horribly bad, Jim and Laurendecide they should never see each other again, until they get stuck with their respective kids at a family resort.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227010000 +0800" stop="20251227030000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Laggies</title>
    <desc lang="en">Feeling overwhelmed by the pressures of being an adult,Megan decides to take a break and hides at the house of a new teenager friend and her single father.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227030000 +0800" stop="20251227050000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Edge of Seventeen</title>
    <desc lang="en">The 17-year-old Nadine tries to make sense of the challengesthrown down her way as she grows up, suffering the depression of losing her father, and a shattered friendship with Krista who dates Nadine's brother, Darian. Nadine finds solace with her teacher, Mr. Bruner, and a talented classmate.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2016)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227050000 +0800" stop="20251227073000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Yesterday</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a global blackout, a struggling musician shockinglydiscovers that he’s the only person on earth who remembers the world renowned music band, The Beatles.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227073000 +0800" stop="20251227093000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Gangster Squad</title>
    <desc lang="en">In late 1940s Los Angeles, a secret crew of determinedpolice officers try to take down a ruthless mob king, whose power and influence extend from his aides to the police, all the way up to the city's politicians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227093000 +0800" stop="20251227120000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Public Enemies</title>
    <desc lang="en">A biopic that chronicles the FBI hunt of the infamous thiefJohn Dillinger and two of his known associates, Baby Face Nelson and Pretty Boy Floyd.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227120000 +0800" stop="20251227140000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Lucky Number Slevin</title>
    <desc lang="en">A case of mistaken identity lands Slevin in the middle of awar between two rival crime bosses. Put under surveillance by a detective and an assassin, he has to plan his move before they make their own.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227140000 +0800" stop="20251227160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Eastern Promises</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a London hospital, a Russian teenager dies while givingbirth, and the midwife finds her diary that contains clues leading to a Russian mob family that has assaulted her.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2007)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227160000 +0800" stop="20251227180000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Black Mass</title>
    <desc lang="en">The film follows the true story of Whitey Bulger, the mostinfamous violent criminal in the history of South Boston, who also happened to be the brother of a state senator, and became an FBI informant to take down a Mafia family invading his turf.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227180000 +0800" stop="20251227193000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">A Bad Moms Christmas</title>
    <desc lang="en">Amy, Kiki, and Carla are three under-appreciated andover-burdened mothers who are trying to cope with their lives when their scary mothers come to visit them for Christmas, bringing the three of them into a new challenge to celebrate Christmas the way they prefer.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227193000 +0800" stop="20251227213000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Edge of Seventeen</title>
    <desc lang="en">The 17-year-old Nadine tries to make sense of the challengesthrown down her way as she grows up, suffering the depression of losing her father, and a shattered friendship with Krista who dates Nadine's brother, Darian. Nadine finds solace with her teacher, Mr. Bruner, and a talented classmate.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2016)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227213000 +0800" stop="20251227233000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Selma</title>
    <desc lang="en">The film focuses on the life of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.,in 1965 when he led marches from Selma to Montgomery, Alabama to demand equal voting rights.&#13;
As the demonstrators faced the police forces, and after many hit-and-run ,their number began to increase in a way that could not be confronted with violence.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227233000 +0800" stop="20251228010000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Paddington</title>
    <desc lang="en">Paddington follows the comic misadventures of a youngPeruvian bear with a passion for all things British, who travels to London in search of a home. Finding himself lost and alone at Paddington Station, he begins to realise that city life is not all he had imagined - until he meets the kindly Brown family, who read the label around his neck ('Please look after this bear. Thank you.') and offer him a temporary haven. It looks as though his luck has changed until this rarest of bears catches the eye of a museum taxidermist.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228010000 +0800" stop="20251228030000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Gangster Squad</title>
    <desc lang="en">In late 1940s Los Angeles, a secret crew of determinedpolice officers try to take down a ruthless mob king, whose power and influence extend from his aides to the police, all the way up to the city's politicians.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2013)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228030000 +0800" stop="20251228050000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Lucky Number Slevin</title>
    <desc lang="en">A case of mistaken identity lands Slevin in the middle of awar between two rival crime bosses. Put under surveillance by a detective and an assassin, he has to plan his move before they make their own.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228050000 +0800" stop="20251228073000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Public Enemies</title>
    <desc lang="en">A biopic that chronicles the FBI hunt of the infamous thiefJohn Dillinger and two of his known associates, Baby Face Nelson and Pretty Boy Floyd.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228073000 +0800" stop="20251228093000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Poseidon</title>
    <desc lang="en">On New Year's Eve, a huge passenger ship is exposed to adangerous wave that capsizes it, and the passengers try to survive at all costs.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228093000 +0800" stop="20251228120000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">2012</title>
    <desc lang="en">Dr. Adrian Helmsley is an American geologist who, while on atrip to India, learns that there has been increased solar activity. Dr. Helmsley also discovers that this will lead to a rise in the temperature of Earth’s core – a phenomenon which will have dire consequences for humanity. 2012 is said to be the end date of the Mayan calendar, which many believe marks the end of the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228120000 +0800" stop="20251228140000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Into the Storm</title>
    <desc lang="en">The town of Silverton is devastated by a wave of deadlytornadoes, and storm trackers predict the worst is yet to come. Meanwhile, a group of high school students document the events and aftermath of the disaster.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228140000 +0800" stop="20251228160000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Impossible</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young British family vacationing in Thailand is suddenlytorn apart when the devastating 2004 tsunami tears through their seaside resort. Their devoted search for one another is a testament to the human spirit and the power of family.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228160000 +0800" stop="20251228173000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Adrift</title>
    <desc lang="en">The true story of, Tami Oldham and Richard Sharp, whosailed across the ocean, but didn't anticipate that they would be sailing directly into one of the most catastrophic hurricanes in recorded history and must stand against all difficulties throughout their journey.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228173000 +0800" stop="20251228200000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Public Enemies</title>
    <desc lang="en">A biopic that chronicles the FBI hunt of the infamous thiefJohn Dillinger and two of his known associates, Baby Face Nelson and Pretty Boy Floyd.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2009)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228200000 +0800" stop="20251228213000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Eastern Promises</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a London hospital, a Russian teenager dies while givingbirth, and the midwife finds her diary that contains clues leading to a Russian mob family that has assaulted her.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2007)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228213000 +0800" stop="20251228233000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Lucky Number Slevin</title>
    <desc lang="en">A case of mistaken identity lands Slevin in the middle of awar between two rival crime bosses. Put under surveillance by a detective and an assassin, he has to plan his move before they make their own.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228233000 +0800" stop="20251229013000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Paddington 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Paddington is happily living with the Brown family inWindsor Gardens, where he becomes a popular member of the community. He finds a special book to give to his Aunt Lucy for her 100th birthday at Mr. Gruber's antique shop, and gets involved in a series of peculiar jobs to buy it.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229013000 +0800" stop="20251229040000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">The Impossible</title>
    <desc lang="en">A young British family vacationing in Thailand is suddenlytorn apart when the devastating 2004 tsunami tears through their seaside resort. Their devoted search for one another is a testament to the human spirit and the power of family.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229040000 +0800" stop="20251229060000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Into the Storm</title>
    <desc lang="en">The town of Silverton is devastated by a wave of deadlytornadoes, and storm trackers predict the worst is yet to come. Meanwhile, a group of high school students document the events and aftermath of the disaster.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229060000 +0800" stop="20251229080000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Adrift</title>
    <desc lang="en">The true story of, Tami Oldham and Richard Sharp, whosailed across the ocean, but didn't anticipate that they would be sailing directly into one of the most catastrophic hurricanes in recorded history and must stand against all difficulties throughout their journey.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229080000 +0800" stop="20251229100000 +0800" channel="mbc max">
    <title lang="en">Line of Duty</title>
    <desc lang="en">After accidentally killing a child abductor, the disgracedcop Frank Penny enters a race against time to find the daughter of the police chief before it's too late.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251226233000 +0800" stop="20251227010000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">My Spy</title>
    <desc lang="en">The tough CIA agent JJ finds himself at the mercy of thewitty 9-year-old girl Sophie, after he is secretly sent to monitor her family.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2020)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227010000 +0800" stop="20251227030000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Four Christmases</title>
    <desc lang="en">The story of a couple struggling to visit all four of theirdivorced parents, and it seems very difficult for everyone to regroup again because of the trouble it brings. Things may be harder than they seem.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2008)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227030000 +0800" stop="20251227050000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Forgetting Sarah Marshall</title>
    <desc lang="en">Peter goes to Hawaii on vacation to try to forget hisgirlfriend the TV star Sarah, who ended their relationship a short time ago, only to find her staying in the same resort with her new boyfriend.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2008)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227050000 +0800" stop="20251227070000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Last Christmas</title>
    <desc lang="en">Kate's life in an unmitigated mess. Despite her dreams ofbeing a singer, she finds herself stuck working as an elf in a year-round Christmas shop. But Kate's life starts to look up when Tom enters her life. Perhaps he can put an end to her string of bad decisions.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227070000 +0800" stop="20251227090000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Jumanji: The Next Level</title>
    <desc lang="en">When a depressed Spencer starts fiddling with the brokenJumanji game in search of purpose, his friends reenter the game to rescue him, along with his grandfather and his old friend. As they encounter a landscape ravaged by drought, they must fight to find Spencer and save Jumanji.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227090000 +0800" stop="20251227110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Stone</title>
    <desc lang="en">Gerald “ Stone” Creeson (Edward Norton) is a convictedarsonist who is spending time in prison. Desperate to get out, Stone has his wife Lucetta (Milla Jovovich) seduce his parole officer Jack Mabrey (Robert De Niro).Stone is playing a dangerous game as his attempts at psychological manipulation could conceivably backfire at any moment – so is the gamble worth the prize?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2010)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227110000 +0800" stop="20251227130000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Vengeance: A Love Story</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a woman was physically assaulted by a group of peopleafter attending a party and getting away with it, John Dromoor, a gulf war veteran who now works as a local police officer decides to take matters into his own hands and bring the woman justice.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227130000 +0800" stop="20251227153000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Equalizer</title>
    <desc lang="en">McCall (Denzel Washington) is a former black ops commandowho has faked his death to live a quiet life in Boston. When he comes out of his self-imposed retirement to rescue a young girl, Teri (Chloë Grace Moretz), he finds himself face to face with notorious Russian gangsters. As he serves vengeance against those who brutalize the helpless, McCall's desire for justice is reawakened.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227153000 +0800" stop="20251227173000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Equalizer 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">Susan Plummer, a close friend of Robert McCall, dies whilelooking into a murder-suicide. He uses his resources and experience as a former spy and marine to track out the assailant and exact revenge on her.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2018)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227173000 +0800" stop="20251227190000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Jolt</title>
    <desc lang="en">A bouncer with a violent anger-management problem uses anelectrode-lined vest to control her homicidal tendencies. But when the man she loves is killed, she sets out on a bloody pursuit to find the murderer.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227190000 +0800" stop="20251227210000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The American</title>
    <desc lang="en">After she is accepted into the notoriously difficult BolshoiBallet Academy in Moscow, the American ballerina Joy Womack feels she is getting closer to achieving her dream of becoming a brilliant ballerina.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2023)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227210000 +0800" stop="20251227233000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Mask of Zorro</title>
    <desc lang="en">Don Diego fights the Spaniards, but he pays dearly when hiswife is murdered and his baby daughter Elena is kidnapped by the corrupt governor Rafael Montero. When Rafael returns to California, Diego decides to take revenge and trains the young Alejandro in martial arts to be his successor.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (1998)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251227233000 +0800" stop="20251228013000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Fred Claus</title>
    <desc lang="en">Santa ,also known as Nicholas,has his brother Fred Clausmoving in with him to the North Pole. Throughout Santa's life, he is always the giving role model while his brother is the complete opposite , living in his shadow all his life. With Christmas getting closer,can he turn things around?</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2007)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228013000 +0800" stop="20251228033000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Pitch Perfect</title>
    <desc lang="en">Beca, a freshman at Barden University, reluctantly joins TheBellas, the school's female acapella group.  Beca shakes up the group's tired repertoire with some fresh ideas and leads the group to nationals, where they take on their crowd-pleasing male rivals.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2012)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228033000 +0800" stop="20251228053000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Vengeance: A Love Story</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a woman was physically assaulted by a group of peopleafter attending a party and getting away with it, John Dromoor, a gulf war veteran who now works as a local police officer decides to take matters into his own hands and bring the woman justice.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228053000 +0800" stop="20251228073000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">G.I. Jane</title>
    <desc lang="en">Under pressure from a female Senator, the U.S. Navyintegrates women into their team, and the first woman to join is Lieutenant Jordan O'Neil, who undergoes arduous training under the command of a man who pushes her to her limits as everyone else expects her to fail.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (1997)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228073000 +0800" stop="20251228090000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Jolt</title>
    <desc lang="en">A bouncer with a violent anger-management problem uses anelectrode-lined vest to control her homicidal tendencies. But when the man she loves is killed, she sets out on a bloody pursuit to find the murderer.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2021)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228090000 +0800" stop="20251228110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Arthur</title>
    <desc lang="en">Arthur ( Russell Brand), a drunken playboy is forced by hismother to marry the successful businesswoman Susan or he will lose his inheritance. But he meets the outgoing girl Naomi, he thinks that she's the one, and he has to choose between love or fortune.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228110000 +0800" stop="20251228130000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Tower Heist</title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of men who work at a tower discover that they arevictims of a wealthy businessman, and that they are part of a plan to steal the tower.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228130000 +0800" stop="20251228150000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Horrible Bosses 2</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Nick, Dale and Curt decide to open their own business,they discover an investor who is trying to take them down. So they decide to kidnap his son Rex, to put up a ransom to take back their business.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228150000 +0800" stop="20251228170000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Vacation</title>
    <desc lang="en">In an attempt to reconnect with his family, Rusty Griswoldtakes his wife and sons on a road trip, hoping it will send them journeying through their relationship, but things go unexpectedly odd.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228170000 +0800" stop="20251228183000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Unfinished Business</title>
    <desc lang="en">A hard-working small business owner and his two associatestravel to Europe to close the most important deal of their lives. But what began as a routine business trip goes off the rails in every imaginable and unimaginable way.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2015)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228183000 +0800" stop="20251228203000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">In the Line of Fire</title>
    <desc lang="en">An aging secret service agent who suffers from the aftermathof the John F. Kennedy assassination in Dallas, receives calls from an unstable man telling him information about his plans to assassinate the current president.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (1993)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228203000 +0800" stop="20251228233000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Equalizer</title>
    <desc lang="en">McCall (Denzel Washington) is a former black ops commandowho has faked his death to live a quiet life in Boston. When he comes out of his self-imposed retirement to rescue a young girl, Teri (Chloë Grace Moretz), he finds himself face to face with notorious Russian gangsters. As he serves vengeance against those who brutalize the helpless, McCall's desire for justice is reawakened.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2014)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251228233000 +0800" stop="20251229010000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Vengeance: A Love Story</title>
    <desc lang="en">After a woman was physically assaulted by a group of peopleafter attending a party and getting away with it, John Dromoor, a gulf war veteran who now works as a local police officer decides to take matters into his own hands and bring the woman justice.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229010000 +0800" stop="20251229030000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Five Feet Apart</title>
    <desc lang="en">Stella is a cystic fibrosis patient who spends her days inthe hospital, without anything exciting about her life, until she meets the rebellious Will who suffers from the same illness and they both change each other's lives.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2019)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229030000 +0800" stop="20251229050000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Tower Heist</title>
    <desc lang="en">A group of men who work at a tower discover that they arevictims of a wealthy businessman, and that they are part of a plan to steal the tower.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2011)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229050000 +0800" stop="20251229070000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">My Super Ex-Girlfriend</title>
    <desc lang="en">When Matt dumps Jenny, who is on the needy side, she usesher superpowers to make his life miserable.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2006)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229070000 +0800" stop="20251229090000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">Bedazzled</title>
    <desc lang="en">Elliot is desperate to win the heart of his dream girlAllison,  he is offered seven wishes by a very persuasive Devil to have what he wants, but in return he must give her his soul.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2000)</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20251229090000 +0800" stop="20251229110000 +0800" channel="mbc 2">
    <title lang="en">The Dark Tower</title>
    <desc lang="en">In a parallel universe, Roland Deschain fights witheverything he has to prevent his enemy, the Man in Black, from bringing down a structure that preserves reality. With the Man in Black trying to use psychic children to unleash darkness, Roland takes one of them in to save both him and the world.</desc>
    <category lang="en">Movie
               (2017)</category>
  </programme>
</tv>
